Gothic II The History of Khorinis
But who knows, maybe I can find a job in merchant guild, located in mines.
Well, it's pretty good paid.
Take a trip to the sunny archipelago, while you are still alive.
I received strict instructions -
no leaks, if you understand.
I have lot to loose.
And no wrong cracks!
Its not as quick, as it was, but it works.
I had to sell my goat, to fix the mill.
Now everything works.
I am not complaining...
Business goes well, I am healthy, that's all I need.
Even a baker from Vaduz sometimes came here, to buy some flour.
Damn it!
I can hear another rat.
I lived for so long...
just to see so many bad things?
Director: Piotr Czołnowski
Audio: Kamil Jędrzejewski
Editing: Doktor Borginson